Nathaniel Barrera

General Engineering Student

Engineering student with 4 years of customer service looking to develop skills related to software architecture and programming as an intern, as well as further building upon soft skills related toward team building and social interaction.

Contact

Address

Round Rock, TX 78664

Phone

(512) 584-0031

E-mail

nbarrera@theplacefornate.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nathaniel-barrera-2587

WWW

http://theplacefornate.com

Skills

- Emphasizes listening over speaking during conversations.
- Remains Calm in stressful environments.
- Practices empathy and understands multiple perspectives

Accomplishments

- Eagle Scout January 2016
- Chevron Engineering Mentorship Program - 2022

Projects

- Connect 4
- theplacefornate.com
- Go!

Education

2022-08 -Current

Bachelor of Science: General Engineering

Texas A&M University - College Station, TX Relevant Courses:

• ENGR-102 (Python3)

2016-08 -2023-05

Associate of Science: Computer Science

Austin Community College - Austin, TX Relevant Courses:

- Programming Fundamentals 1 (Python3)
- Programming Fundamentals 2 (C++)
- Programming Fundamentals 3 (C++)
- Machine Learning

Work History

2020-05 -Current

Material Fulfillment Specialist

Bare Performance Nutrition, Round Rock, Texas

- Collaborated with departments across the company, including marketing and project management, in creating new ideas, initiatives, products, and services.
- Developed and maintained relationships with 10 new staff members, and focused on creating core conversational and resolution skills.
- Ensures time is made for each item ordered is sent correctly to ensure customer satisfaction.

2016-08 -2020-06

Central Service Cashier

H-E-B, Round Rock, Texas

- Provided unique customer service skills, keeping customers engaged and satisfied.
- Engaged with customers to ensure they found items they were looking for.
- Demonstrated attention to detail and patience by resolving customer's issues.

Hobbies

- Enjoys collecting and listening to vinyl records.
- Makes time to go to the gym to be in my thoughts.
- Loves being up to date with tech and seeing how much technology improves over time.